<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Saudi Arabian Founders Toolkit on Our research provides clear guidance, offering a path for young Saudi Arabain entrepreneurs with a vision to invent their desired future</title>
    <link>https://saudifounders.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Saudi Arabian Founders Toolkit on Our research provides clear guidance, offering a path for young Saudi Arabain entrepreneurs with a vision to invent their desired future</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 19:40:08 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://saudifounders.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Key Personality Types</title>
      <link>https://saudifounders.org/docs/key-personality-types-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 18:30:08 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://saudifounders.org/docs/key-personality-types-1/</guid>
      <description>Entrepreneurs between 18 and 30 boost innovation and economic growth with their fresh perspectives and technological know-how. They are uniquely positioned to leverage emerging technologies and societal trends, bringing about transformative changes across various sectors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Spirit of Discovery</title>
      <link>https://saudifounders.org/docs/the-spirit-of-discovery-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 19:40:08 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://saudifounders.org/docs/the-spirit-of-discovery-2/</guid>
      <description>For entrepreneurs, curiosity drives discovery and innovation, shaping the path to success. Embracing the ability to question and explore is vital, guiding them through uncharted territories and propelling their journey forward.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://saudifounders.org/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 18:30:08 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://saudifounders.org/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>Contact Details For SaudiFounders.org</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lean Creator Mindset</title>
      <link>https://saudifounders.org/docs/the-lean-creator-mindset-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 19:30:08 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://saudifounders.org/docs/the-lean-creator-mindset-3/</guid>
      <description>We will discover a world where people can create using natural human language, significantly improving computers&amp;rsquo; capabilities. Instead of people adapting to computers, computers will adapt to people, making technology accessible to everyone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering The Lean Launch</title>
      <link>https://saudifounders.org/docs/mastering-the-lean-launch-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:30:08 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://saudifounders.org/docs/mastering-the-lean-launch-4/</guid>
      <description>Startups and founders, regardless of their archetype, often encounter significant hurdles that can make or break their ventures. The most common and challenging obstacle is obtaining funding, a pursuit that can seem endless and overwhelming.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathway to Sustainability</title>
      <link>https://saudifounders.org/docs/pathway-to-sustainability-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 15:30:08 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://saudifounders.org/docs/pathway-to-sustainability-5/</guid>
      <description>To innovate sustainably, leverage your strengths and address weaknesses. Our framework helps founders identify and develop core skills while providing practical strategies to overcome shortcomings, fostering resilience and adaptability for lasting success.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Classy Startups</title>
      <link>https://saudifounders.org/docs/the-classy-startups-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 19:35:08 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://saudifounders.org/docs/the-classy-startups-6/</guid>
      <description>Launching a startup on a tight budget is challenging. Our study offers practical tips and strategies for building a successful business from scratch, focusing on cost-effective methods and resourceful approaches tailored for aspiring entrepreneurs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Startups of Arabia</title>
      <link>https://saudifounders.org/docs/the-kingom-of-saudi-arabia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2024 17:30:08 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://saudifounders.org/docs/the-kingom-of-saudi-arabia/</guid>
      <description>This study is based on a policy perspective as a roadmap for young innovators. It aims to provide a strategic framework to support and nurture entrepreneurship within the kingdom. By focusing on critical areas of development, this study outlines how targeted policies can create an environment conducive to the growth of startups and small businesses.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
